Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
- Box: 96, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Wages Structure and Level of Pay for Dock Workers, 1966; Publication (Box 96, Folder 20)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Labor
- Box: 96, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Davis-Bacon Act, Publication (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: The Walsh-Healey Act, Publication (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Inflation's Helpmate, Publication (Box 96, Folder 21)
- Box: 96, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Wet Minimumloon en Minimumvakantiebijslag, 1970; Publication (Box 96, Folder 22)
    Author: G.G.A. den Dulk
    Language: Dutch.
  - Item 2: Law of Minimum Wages, 1967; Publication (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: A National Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 96, Folder 22)
- Box: 96, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Laborers' & Mechanics' Minimum Rates of Pay, 1966; Publication (Box 96, Folder 23)
    Author: Alaska Department of Labor
- Box: 96, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Minimum Wage Rates in Canada, 1972; Publication (Box 96, Folder 24)
    Notes: January 2, 1972
  - Item 2: Special Tables on Living Costs and Wages, 1972; Publication (Box 96, Folder 24)
    Author: Ontario Department of Labour
    Notes: December 13, 1972
  - Item 3: Minimum Wage Order, 1965; Publication (Box 96, Folder 24)
    Author: Province of Nova Scotia
    Notes: February 20, 1965
  - Item 4: Minimum Wage Order, 1965; Publication (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Minimum Wage Order, 1965; Publication (Box 96, Folder 24)
    Notes: May 8, 1965
- Box: 96, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Regional Round-Table Seminar on Minimum Wages in National Development, 1967; Publication (Box 96, Folder 25)
    Notes: June 5-10, 1967
- Box: 96, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Public Law 89-684, 1966; Publication (Box 96, Folder 26)
    Notes: October 15, 1966
  - Item 2: District of Columbia Minimum Wage Law, 1965; Publication (Box 96, Folder 26)
    Notes: October 12, 1965
- Box: 96, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Salario Minimo, Publication (Box 96, Folder 27)
    Author: Guatemala Ministerio de Trabajo
- Box: 96, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Law of Minimum Wages, Publication (Box 96, Folder 28)
    Author: Attar Singh Talbgar
- Box: 96, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employment in Tile Industry, Publication (Box 96, Folder 29)
    Author: Government of Kerala
  - Item 2: Employment in Cardamom Plantations, Publication (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Printing Presses, 1958; Publication (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Toddy Tapping Industry, Publication (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Revision of the Minimum Wages for Employment Under Municipalities, Publication (Box 96, Folder 29)
- Box: 96, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Aspects of Minimum Wage Systems in Latin America, 1967; Publication (Box 96, Folder 30)
    Author: Inter-American Conference of Ministers of Labor
    Notes: June 12-14, 1967
- Box: 96, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Minimum Wage Rates in Effect Under Massachusetts Wage Orders, 1967; Publication (Box 96, Folder 31)
    Notes: February 1, 1967
- Box: 96, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: New Jersey State Wage & Hour Law, Publication (Box 96, Folder 32)
    Author: New Jersey Legislature
  - Item 2: Wage Orders Covering Women and Minors, Publication (Box 96, Folder 32)
    Author: New Jersey Wage and Hour Bureau
- Box: 96, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Minimum Wages in Grocery Stores, Publication (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Economic Effects of Minimum Wages, Publication (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Report of the Hotel Minimum Wage Board to the Industrial Commissioner, 1961; Publication (Box 96, Folder 33)
    Notes: August 21, 1961
- Box: 96, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours in Industries Covered by the Minimum Wage Law, Publication (Box 96, Folder 34)
- Box: 96, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Minimum Wage Orders, 1966; Publication (Box 96, Folder 35)
    Author: North Dakota Department of Agriculture and Labor
    Notes: April 5, 1966
- Box: 96, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: An Act Respecting Minimum Wages, 1964; Publication (Box 96, Folder 36)
    Author: Nova Scotia Legislature
    Notes: March 18, 1964
- Box: 96, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 96, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: A Living Wage by Legislation, Publication (Box 96, Folder 37)
    Author: Edwin V. O'Hara
- Box: 96, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 96, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Law of Minimum Wages, 1962; Publication (Box 96, Folder 38)
    Author: Bureau of Labour Publications
  - Item 2: The Construction, Business Service, Banking, Insurance, Finance, and Motion Picture Industry in Puerto Rico, 1961; Publication (Box 96, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Minimum Wages, 1969; Publication (Box 96, Folder 38)
    Author: British Columbia Federation of Labour
    Notes: December 3, 1969
- Box: 96, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The Sugarcane Industry in Puerto Rico, 1969; Publication (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: The General Agriculture Industry in Puerto Rico, 1969; Publication (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: Agriculture in Puerto Rico, 1967; Publication (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: The Restaurant and Food Service Industry in Puerto Rico, 1967; Publication (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: The Hotel and Motel Industry in Puerto Rico, 1967; Publication (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Item 6: Other Newly Covered Activities Industry in Puerto Rico, 1967; Publication (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Item 7: The Tobacco Industry in Puerto Rico, 1964; Publication (Box 96, Folder 39)
- Box: 96, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 96, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: State Minimum Wage Act, 1965; Publication (Box 96, Folder 40)
    Author: Rhode Island Department of Labor
- Box: 96, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 96, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Minimum Wages, Wages Councils and Conditions of Employment, 1964; Publication (Box 96, Folder 41)
    Author: Northern Rhodesia Legislature
- Box: 97, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Minimum Wage and its Impact on South Carolina, 1968; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Author: James E. Estes
    Notes: July 1968
  - Item 2: Fact File on the Impact of Minimum Wages on Employment, Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Should the Federal Minimum Wage be Lower for Youth than for Adults?, 1973; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Notes: January 29, 1973
  - Item 4: Some Effects of a Minimum Wage Upon the Economy as a Whole, Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Economics of Minimum Wage Legislation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Author: George J. Stigler
  - Item 6: The Minimum Wage, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Author: The Free Society
  - Item 7: Minimum Wage Increases, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Box: 97, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: On the Home Front with Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Economics of Minimum Wage Legislation, 1947; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: June 1947
  - Item 3: Minimum Wage and the Woman Worker, 1958; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: January 1, 1958
  - Item 4: Minimum Wage and the Woman Worker, 1955; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Author: Massachusetts Department of Labor and Industries
  - Item 6: Minimum Wage, 1949; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: January 1949
  - Item 7: Draft Minimum Wage Order for Hotel and Restaurant Occupations, 1941; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 2, 1941
  - Item 8: State Minimum-Wage Law and Order Provisions Affecting Working Conditions, 1961; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Minimum Wages and Government Contracts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Author: Herbert C. Morton
  - Item 10: The High Cost of Low Wages, 1939; Publication (Box 97, Folder 2)
    Notes: August 1, 1939
- Box: 97, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: State Minimum Wage Legislation, 1969; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Brief Summary of State Minimum Wage Laws, 1964; Publication (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 1964
- Box: 97, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: State Minimum Wage Legislation, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 4)
    Notes: June 1966
- Box: 97, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Hotels and Motels, 1969; Publication (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Box: 97, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Need for More Realistic Minimum Wage Rate Determinations for Certain Federally Financed Housing in Washington Metropolitan Area, 1968; Publication (Box 97, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 13, 1968
- Box: 97, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: West Virginia Prevailing Minimum Wage Law, Publication (Box 97, Folder 7)
    Author: University of West Virginia
- Box: 97, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: La Politique Neerlandaise des Salaires, 1902; Publication (Box 97, Folder 8)
    Author: Societe Belge d'Etudes & d'Expansion
    Notes: February 24, 1902
- Box: 97, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: General Wage Orders, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 9)
    Author: New Zealand Government
  - Item 2: Factors Affecting Wage and Salary Levels in New Zealand, 1968; Publication (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Box: 97, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Extra Pay for Long Service, 1964; Publication (Box 97, Folder 10)
    Notes: September 15, 1964
  - Item 2: Les Modes de Remuneration et les Sciences Sociales du Travail en Grande-Bretagne, Publication (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Salary Administration and Manpower Planning, Publication (Box 97, Folder 10)
    Author: Social Organisation Limited
- Box: 97, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Railroad Mileage Pay and Piece Rates in Other Industries, 1961; Publication (Box 97, Folder 11)
    Author: Carriers' Conference Committees
    Notes: February 1961
  - Item 2: Parkhurst Differential Bonus Plan, Publication (Box 97, Folder 11)
    Author: Frederic A. Parkhurst
  - Item 3: Relationships Between Wages, 1951; Publication (Box 97, Folder 11)
    Author: Richard P. Calhoon
- Box: 97, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Wages in Australia, Publication (Box 97, Folder 12)
    Author: Australian Council of Employers' Federations
  - Item 2: Prevalence of Incentive Payment Systems, 1967; Publication (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Systems of Wage Payment, Publication (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Lonnssystemer, Publication (Box 97, Folder 12)
    Author: Finn A. Madsen
  - Item 5: Ackordsloner, Publication (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Material and Moral Incentives Under Socialism, Publication (Box 97, Folder 12)
    Author: Mikhail Laptin
- Box: 97, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Die Weihnachtsgratifikation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
    Author: Kurt Haberkorn
- Box: 97, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Irregular, Unscheduled, Overtime Differential, 1968; Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
- Box: 97, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Wage Theory, Wage Rates and Productivity, Publication (Box 97, Folder 15)
    Author: Joseph H. Taggart, Clifford D. Clark
  - Item 2: Wages and Prices, Publication (Box 97, Folder 15)
    Author: John T. Dunlop
  - Item 3: Wages, Prices, Profits, Productivity, 1959; Publication (Box 97, Folder 15)
    Author: University of California
    Notes: October 1-4, 1959
  - Item 4: Wages, Prices, Profits, and Productivity, Publication (Box 97, Folder 15)
    Author: University of Texas
- Box: 97, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Testimony, 1941; Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
    Notes: September 29, 1941
- Box: 97, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Premium Pay Practices in Private Industry, Publication (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Wage Survey Report for the Tristate Area, 1950; Publication (Box 97, Folder 17)
    Author: Tristate Industrial Association
    Notes: April 1950
- Box: 97, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Wages, Hours and Overtime Pay Provisions in Selected Industries, 1968; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
    Notes: June 1968
  - Item 2: Negotiated Wage Rates in Ontario Hospitals, 1969; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Estudio Economico, 1964; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Monografias, 1965; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Wage, Salary, and Fringe Benefit, 1965; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
    Author: Wisconsin Department of Administration
    Notes: March 1965
  - Item 6: American Samoa, 1969; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Reported Employment and Earnings in Kenya, 1962; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
    Author: Kenya Ministry of Finance and Economic Planning
  - Item 8: Minimum Wage Rates, Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
    Author: Australia Bureau of Census and Statistics
  - Item 9: Average Weekly Earnings of Workers, Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
    Author: Ohio Bureau of Unemployment Compensation
  - Item 10: Occupational Wage Survey, 1953; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
    Notes: November 1953
  - Item 11: Average Weekly Wages in Covered Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
    Author: Louisiana Department of Labor
  - Item 12: Burlington, Vermont, Wage Survey, Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Wages and Salaries in Waterbury, Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: Wages and Salaries in Manchester, Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Wages and Salaries in New Haven, Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Earnings and Work Experience, 1967; Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
- Box: 97, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Wages of Agricultural Labor, Publication (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: The Application of Minimum Wages in Agriculture, 1967; Publication (Box 97, Folder 19)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Agriculture
    Notes: February 27, 1967
  - Item 3: Farm Labor and Minimum Wages, Publication (Box 97, Folder 19)
    Author: North Carolina Agricultural Extension Service
  - Item 4: Report of the Non-Plantation Agricultural Workers Minimum Wages Board, 1963; Publication (Box 97, Folder 19)
    Author: Non-Plantation Agricultural Workers Minimum Wages Board
- Box: 97, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Earnings of Migratory Farm Workers in Wayne County, 1969; Publication (Box 97, Folder 20)
    Author: Herrington J. Bryce
- Box: 97, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Earnings and Hours of Women Agricultural Workers, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
- Box: 97, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Average Hourly Earnings in Arkansas Manufacturing, 1967; Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
    Author: University of Arkansas
  - Item 2: Average Hourly Earnings in Arkansas, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
- Box: 97, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Arizona Prevailing Wage Scale, Publication (Box 97, Folder 23)
    Author: Arizona Industrial Commission
- Box: 97, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Bread and Confectionery Industry, 1960; Publication (Box 97, Folder 24)
    Author: South Africa Legislation
    Notes: November 4, 1960
- Box: 97, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Wages and Salaries for Selected Occupations, 1970; Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Wages and Salaries for Selected Occupations, 1970; Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
- Box: 97, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Wages and Salaries in Boston, 1964; Publication (Box 97, Folder 26)
- Box: 97, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Wage and Hour Law and the Building Industry After Ten Years, 1948; Publication (Box 97, Folder 27)
    Notes: October 27, 1948
- Box: 97, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing, Mining and Logging, 1948; Publication (Box 97, Folder 28)
    Author: Canada Department of Trade and Commerce
    Notes: June 25, 1948
- Box: 97, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The Behavior of Canadian Wages and Salaries in the Postwar Period, Publication (Box 97, Folder 29)
- Box: 97, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Estudio Economico, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Estudio Economico Para la Determinacion del Salario Minimo en la Industria de Substancias y Productos Quimicos, 1965; Publication (Box 97, Folder 30)
- Box: 97, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Comparison of Certain Basic Wage Rates and Cost of Fringe Benefits, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 31)
    Author: The Civic Federation
  - Item 2: Prevailing Wage Rates, 1964; Publication (Box 97, Folder 31)
- Box: 97, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Pay Structure of the Federal Civil Service, 1961; Publication (Box 97, Folder 32)
    Notes: June 30, 1961
- Box: 97, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Contract Cleaning Services, 1961; Publication (Box 97, Folder 33)
    Notes: Summer 1961
- Box: 97, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Men's and Boys' Shirts, 1961; Publication (Box 97, Folder 34)
    Notes: May-June 1961
- Box: 97, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Bituminous-Coal Mines, 1951; Publication (Box 97, Folder 35)
    Author: Monthly Labor Review
- Box: 97, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Employee and Compensation Data by Occupational Classification, 1950; Publication (Box 97, Folder 36)
    Notes: October 1950
- Box: 97, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 97, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Background Information Concerning Confectionery Industry, Publication (Box 97, Folder 37)
- Box: 97, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 97, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Local Wage Rates for Selected Occupations, Publication (Box 97, Folder 38)
    Author: U.S. Works Progress Administration
  - Item 2: The Escalation of Wages in Construction, Publication (Box 97, Folder 38)
    Author: Alan Greenspan
  - Item 3: Construction Costs for Certain Federally Financed Housing Projects Increased Due to Inappropriate Minimum Wage Rate Determinations, 1970; Publication (Box 97, Folder 38)
    Notes: August 12, 1970
  - Item 4: Building and Construction Workers Guide, 1960; Publication (Box 97, Folder 38)
    Notes: October 1960
- Box: 97, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Estudio Economico, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: State Contract Highway Construction, 1969; Publication (Box 97, Folder 39)
    Author: Wisconsin Department of Industry
    Notes: April 30, 1969
  - Item 3: Salaires, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 39)
    Author: Confederation Nationale de la Construction
    Notes: April 27, 1966
  - Item 4: Rasta ane Makana Bandhakama Vyavasaya Mateni Laghutama Vetana Salahakara Samitino Ahevala, 1966; Publication (Box 97, Folder 39)
    Language: Gujarati.
  - Item 5: Estudio Economico para la Determinacion del Salario Minimo en la Industria de la Construccion, 1965; Publication (Box 97, Folder 39)
- Box: 97, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 97, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: The Changes in Real Wages of Construction Workers, 1963; Publication (Box 97, Folder 40)
    Author: Yohko Sano
- Box: 98, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Arizona Wage Statistics and Copper Output, 1966; Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Author: Arizona Employment Security Commission
- Box: 98, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Earnings in Cotton Textile Mills, 1949; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: April 1949
  - Item 2: Hourly Earnings in Cotton Textile Mills, 1948; Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 23, 1948
- Box: 98, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Prevailing Wages and hours of Employees in the Dairy Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    Author: Hawaii Department of Labor
    Notes: April 1946
- Box: 98, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Monografia para la Determinacion del Salario Minimo en la Industria de Alcoholes, Bebidas Alcoholicas, Destiladas y Fermentadas, 1965; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Notes: May 1965
  - Item 2: Monografia, 1966; Publication (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Box: 98, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Wage Structure, 1950; Publication (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Box: 98, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Electric Utility Workers Average $1.58 an Hour, 1951; Publication (Box 98, Folder 6)
    Notes: April 20, 1951
- Box: 98, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Machinery Manufacturing, 1963; Publication (Box 98, Folder 7)
    Notes: March-May 1963
  - Item 2: Machinery Manufacturing, 1962; Publication (Box 98, Folder 7)
    Notes: March-June 1962
  - Item 3: Machinery Manufacturing, 1961; Publication (Box 98, Folder 7)
    Notes: March-May 1961
- Box: 98, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Salaries of Personnel in State and State-Aided Programs for Mentally Ill and Mentally Retarded, 1966; Publication (Box 98, Folder 8)
    Author: Interstate Clearing House on Mental Health
- Box: 98, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Memorandum, 1967; Publication (Box 98, Folder 9)
    Author: Engineering Workers' Union of South Africa
    Notes: July 5, 1967
- Box: 98, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Employment and Earnings of Migrant Farm Workers in New York State, 1960; Publication (Box 98, Folder 10)
    Notes: August 1960
- Box: 98, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Monografia para la Determinacion del Salario Minimo en la Industria de Teatros y Cines, 1965; Publication (Box 98, Folder 11)
    Notes: June 1965
  - Item 2: Monografia, 1966; Publication (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Box: 98, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Wages, Earnings, and Payrolls, 1947; Publication (Box 98, Folder 12)
    Author: Hawaii Employers Council
    Notes: April 1947
- Box: 98, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Glass and Glassware Manufacturing Industry, 1962; Publication (Box 98, Folder 13)
    Author: South Africa Legislature
    Notes: August 3, 1962
- Box: 98, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Economic Journal, 1962; Publication (Box 98, Folder 14)
    Author: Macmillan and Co.
  - Item 2: The Guardian Wage Indexes, Publication (Box 98, Folder 14)
    Author: Ely Devons, J.R. Crossley
  - Item 3: Rates of Wages and Normal Working Hours in the Principal Industries, 1971; Publication (Box 98, Folder 14)
    Author: Confederation of British Industry
    Notes: June 1971
- Box: 98, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Pay Rates for Office Workers in Hawaii, 1952; Publication (Box 98, Folder 15)
    Notes: August 1952
  - Item 2: Wage-Rates for Warehousing and Trucking Jobs, 1948; Publication (Box 98, Folder 15)
    Notes: April 1948
- Box: 98, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Eating and Drinking Places, 1961; Publication (Box 98, Folder 16)
    Notes: June 1961
  - Item 2: Hotels and Motels, 1961; Publication (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Hotels and Motels, 1963; Publication (Box 98, Folder 16)
    Notes: June 1963